# Chhaganlal B S

Payroll and Implementation Specialist

I am a motivated and analytical payroll specialist with more than 2.5 years of experience in payroll services, specialized in project implementation. In my current role, I have been responsible for rolling out a new automation program that has helped more people in my team to achieve the larger payroll implementation project in a short span of time. I am proud of my solid track record of delivering projects that have had proven business benefits and am now looking to take on greater responsibility.

chaganlal17@gmail.com

PLOT NO 10 180/181 NAVARATHINAPURAM 3RD STREET, KAMARAJAR SALAI, Madurai, India

linkedin.com/in/chhaganlal-b-s-425405107

live:chhaganlal.sundararajan

#### +91-962-919-9050

chhaganlal17.github.io/po/

@chaganlal17

github.com/Chhaganlal17

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Team Lead

Neeyamo Enterprise Solutions Pvt Ltd

12/2020 - Present

- As TL, I'm handling multiple countries EMEA (Morocco, Kenya, Nigeria, South Africa, Egypt, and Tunisia) and in AMER Region (Chile, Peru, and Panama)
- Have Implemented both integration (Workday) and nonintegration projects for 15+countries
- Well versed in payroll training. So far, I have trained around 200+ employees in Payroll, Implementation, and Configuration process
- Knowledge on HRIS integration via workday
- Handling 6 countries with 3000+payslips monthly for monthly, weekly, semi-monthly, and bi-weekly basis
- Performing audit activities as per the regulations to make sure that the process is improved without any deviation
- Handling shadow payroll scenarios by analyzing the COC

### **Associate Team Lead**

Neevamo Enterprise Solutions Pvt Ltd

06/2018 - 11/2020

Tasks

- Handled more than 1000+ headcount in a monthly, bi-weekly, and weekly basis
- Act as a lead, to assign the work and driving the team to achieve the 100% accuracy rate within the SLA
- Collecting, calculating, and entering data in order to maintain and update payroll information
- Compiling summaries of earning, taxes, deduction, leave, and non-taxable wages and reporting on this
- Establish strong client relationships and deliver sustained stable payroll operations
- Responding to employee queries quickly by identifying and resolving their issues

## **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Engineering (EEE)

Sethu Institute of Technology

08/2014 - 05/2018 7.7

SPVM Higher Secondary School

06/2013 - 04/2014 79.9%

SSLC

06/2011 - 04/2012

SPVM Higher Secondary School

# **SKILLS**



#### **PROJECTS**

#### Payroll Implementation

Have Implemented payroll for countries like Nigeria, Morocco, Tunisia, Germany, Australia and New Zealand, etc.

#### Payroll Inhouse Project

Payroll process for Countries namely Tunisia, Morocco and Cameroon has been processed in-house for various clients

#### **Automation Project**

Using Selenium Automation, have automated the configuration process for various modules

#### System Setup

Country logics have been well analyzed and those logics have been accommodated in the Neeyamo's payroll system for multiple countries

### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Extra Mile award for best outstanding performance (08/2018 - 09/2018)

And in May 2020, awarded extra mile again

Wow award for going above and beyond call of duty in (04/2019 - 06/2019)

Torch Bearer Award for Project implementation (11/2020)

Nominated for the employee of the year award 2021

Have completed advanced excel courses in Udemy

### **LANGUAGES**

**Enalish** Full Professional Proficiency

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Hindi

Professional Working Proficiency

85.2%